1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser("")
29. navigateToUrl(URL)
33. maximizeWindow()
37. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
41. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
45. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
49. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
61. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
65. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
69. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
73. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
77. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
81. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)
85. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/btn_continue"))
89. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), 10)
93. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
97. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
105. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Address"), randomAddress)
109. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
113. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Province"))
117. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
121. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Select Province"))
125. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Khan Chamkar Mon_Select_Province"))
129. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Districts"))
133. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Sangkat Tonle Basak_Districts"))
137. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-save"))
141. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Online Payment - WeChat"))
145. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Checkbox__I accept"))
149. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Checkout_Payment"))
153. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/iframe_payment_online"), 7)
157. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/iframe_payment_online"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
161. delay(10)
165. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Approve"))
169. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"), 10)
173. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"), 0)
177. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/button_Continue shopping"))
181. comment("Email      : " + randomEmail)
185. comment("First Name : " + randomFirstName)
189. comment("Last Name  : " + randomLastName)
193. comment("Phone      : " + randomPhone)
197. comment("Address    : " + randomAddress)
201. comment("Code    : " + randomCode)
205. takeScreenshot()
209. closeBrowser()